

I'm an innovative software engineer & leader, with a knack for UI/X design. I specialize in building consumerfacing mobile applications, as-well-as the SDK's & libraries that support them. With 10+ years of experience, I can turn things on their heads, think outside the box, and above all else - put usability and simplicity at the center of my development process.

Education

2013 | BS

COMPUTER SCIENCE

Central Washington University

2011 | AA

NATURAL SCIENCE

Green River Community College

Skills & Highlights

- Swift, Objective-C, C++, C#, Node.js, TypeScript, Nest.js, Vapor, & Go experience
- iOS, iPadOS, watchOS, tvOS, visionOS & Android platform knowledge
- Modern architecture using MVVM, DI, & reactive frameworks (Combine / Rx)
- Modern dependency management using SPM & Cocoapods
- CI automation (Github Actions, Xcode Server, Fastlane, & Jenkins)
- Experience leading & scaling engineering teams
- Startup, B2B, & M&A experience
- Coffee snob **Yes**, this is a skill 😀 🍮

Experience

2024 - PRESENT

FETCH | MADISON, WI (REMOTE) | APP STORE | PLAY STORE

Develop and maintain the Fetch Rewards iOS application & core libraries.

2023 - 2024

LEAD IOS ENGINEER

FISKER | MANHATTAN BEACH, CA (REMOTE) | APP STORE | PLAY STORE

Developed and maintained the Fisker iOS application & core libraries. Lead the team's transition to a modern architecture using SwiftUI, Combine, MVVM, DI, services, & navigators.

2023 - 2024

ENGINEERING LEAD

WING | LOS ANGELES, CA (REMOTE)

Lead a team of engineers across mobile, backend, & frontend web. Architected the Wing tech-stack, iOS application, & support libraries. Work with SLT on brand, design, investment, & marketing efforts.

2019 - 2023

MOBILE LEAD

AIRVET | LOS ANGELES, CA (REMOTE) | APP STORE | PLAY STORE

Lead a team of mobile engineers across both iOS & Android platforms. Architected the Airvet parent & doctor iOS applications & support libraries. Worked closely with product, design, & SL teams for roadmap & product planning.

2018 - 2019

SP. IOS ENGINEER

AUTOGRAVITY | IRVINE, CA

Developed and maintained first-party and white-label applications, libraries, & tools. Managed iOS release automation & CI pipeline.

2016 - 2018

TV TIME / WHIPCLIP | SANTA MONICA, CA | APP STORE | PLAY STORE

Developed and maintained the Whipclip iOS application, as well as the project's transition into TV Time; via company acquisition. Led the migration effort from Objective-C - Swift. Worked alongside product and design teams for a complete re-branding & UI/X overhaul.

2015 - 2016

LEAD IOS ENGINEER

FUSION OF IDEAS | LAKE FOREST, CA

Lead a team of mobile engineers across both iOS & Android platforms. Developed & maintained iOS B2B applications and underlying frameworks for several high-profile clients.







E mitchtreece@me.com P 253.906.0972

Made with ♥ in Las Vegas, NV 😇

